In the game of life, you can't lose 'em all.
Win Win is a drama, comedy film directed by Tom McCarthy.
When down-on-his-luck part-time high school wrestling coach Mike agrees to become legal guardian to an elderly man, his ward's
troubled grandson turns out to be a star grappler, sparking dreams of a big win -- until the boy's mother retrieves him.
Mike Flaherty, played by Paul Giamatti.
Jackie Flaherty, played by Amy Ryan.
Terry Delfino, played by Bobby Cannavale.
Vigman, played by Jeffrey Tambor.
Leo Poplar, played by Burt Young.
Cindy Timmons, played by Melanie Lynskey.
Win Win is a 2011 American sports comedy-drama film written, directed, and
co-produced by Tom McCarthy from a story by McCarthy and Joe Tiboni.
It stars Paul Giamatti as a struggling attorney who, volunteering as a high-school wrestling coach, takes on
the guardianship of an elderly client in a desperate attempt to keep his practice afloat.
Alex Shaffer, Amy Ryan, Bobby Cannavale, and Jeffrey
Tambor appear in supporting roles.
The film had its world premiere at the Sundance Film Festival on January 21, 2011, and was
theatrically released in the United States on March 18, 2011, by Fox Searchlight Pictures.
It grossed over $11.8 million worldwide against a $5 million budget, and received positive reviews
from critics, who mostly praised McCarthy's screenplay and the performances of the cast.
It was named one of the top 10 independent films of 2011 by the National Board of Review, while McCarthy and Tiboni were nominated for
Best Original Screenplay at the 17th Critics' Choice Awards and for Best Screenplay at the 27th Independent Spirit Awards.
The film explores themes of new jersey, sports, coach, lawyer, wrestling coach.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.